hey everybody welcome to this a2 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as I speak before we
start remember to subscribe to the
channel click on the bell and follow us
on Instagram you ready so today I'm
gonna talk about fears this is an
interesting topic because there are so
many fears that exist some people are
afraid of some things that other people
have no problem with that's why I think
that fear is a very personal thing let's
start with one of the most common fears
Heights I would guess that almost half
of the people that I know are afraid of
heights this is a really natural thing
though because being up high often means
danger anybody would be afraid of
falling from a high place however some
people have a more extreme fear of
heights
they usually hate flying and they never
walk near the edge of high places I
don't usually have a problem with
Heights
but there have been times when I got a
little nervous when I looked over the
edge of a high place but I don't have
any fear of flying except sometimes
during takeoff and landing how about you
are you afraid of heights or flying
alright another really common fear is
the fear of spiders or bugs in general
if you or someone you know has this fear
then you know it can be a really intense
fear for some people if they see even
just a little spider in their room they
run away screaming I'm not terrified of
all spiders but if there's a really big
spider that I'm definitely afraid I
think most people in the world would be
afraid of a really big spider one thing
that scares me more than spiders is
cockroaches for me these
the worst I know that they can't hurt me
but I just really hate them if I see a
big cockroach in my room or in the
bathroom I get pretty freaked out I
can't handle cockroaches all right so
another common fear is the fear of the
dark I think that everyone has at least
a little fear of the dark
of course most adults aren't super
afraid of the dark and most situations
but in some situations they can be
afraid for example if you're alone in a
forest at night I'm sure you'll be at
least a little afraid of the dark I'm
not that scared of the dark but
obviously I might get a little nervous
if I'm alone in a dark forest or
something okay
lastly let's talk about the fear of
clowns this is a really popular one and
it's not just a childhood fear a lot of
adults are afraid of clowns - I've never
had a problem with this fear but I know
several people that do I can understand
why people might be afraid of them
because they look really creepy and of
course there are several movies that
feature killer clowns that also
contribute to people's fear of clowns
even though I'm not afraid of clowns I
don't really like them alright that's
all for today leave a comment and tell
me what your greatest fear is and
remember to subscribe to the channel
click on the Bell and follow us on
Instagram for more English tips and
lessons I'll see you next time
[Music]
[Applause]